# Nikia Roberts

# **Machine Operator - International Paper (Box Plant)**

Savannah, GA 31404 nikiaroberts28@gmail.com 912.657.9593

Dependable Machine Attendant able to read and adhere to standard operating procedures. Detailoriented and industrious professional with strong problem-solving abilities. Prepared to bring 5 years of experience to a challenging new position.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

# **Machine Operator**

International Paper (Box Plant) - Savannah, GA January 2016 to Present

Set up and verified the functionality of safety equipment.

Set and monitored product standards, examining samples of raw products and processing tests, to ensure the quality of all finished products.

Ensured that all health and safety guidelines were followed.

Carry out production, inspection, packaging and machine operation duties

#### **School Bus Driver**

Reliant Transportation - Savannah, GA July 2014 to January 2016

Transport children to and from school in the mornings and afternoons

Ensure safety of all students

Obey all traffic laws

Inspected and maintained vehicle supplies and equipment, such as gas, oil, water, tires, lights, and brakes, to ensure that vehicles are in proper working condition

#### **Production Worker**

Strength of Nature/Horizon Staffing - Savannah, GA April 2013 to August 2014

Assembled products according to standardized procedures.

Monitored machine operation and diagnosed malfunctions.

Set up and verified the functionality of safety equipment.

Made sure that products were produced on time and are of good quality.

Responsible for achieving production requirements.

#### **Production Worker**

Roger Wood Foods Inc - Savannah, GA October 2011 to December 2013

Assembled products according to standardized procedures.

Located and picked merchandise to fulfill customer orders. Read and followed standard operating procedures. Set up and verified the functionality of safety equipment.

# Education

## **Associate of Science**

Surgical Technology Technical College of the Lowcountry - Beaufort, SC 2015

#### **Associate of Science**

Savannah Technical College - Savannah, GA 2001

## **High School Diploma in Health Sciences**

Sol. C. Johnson High School - Savannah, GA 2000

#### Skills

#### ORGANIZATIONAL SKILLS

# Additional Information

#### **SKILLS**

Exceptional organizational skills Interpersonal skills Self-motivated Team leadership Strong verbal communication Chemical processing skillfulness Production procedures Extremely quick learner